<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jinji</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jinji</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>一个人的考试</title>
      <link>/cn/2021-12-23-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/2021-12-23-/</guid>
      <description>本人于一周前完成了博士资格考试，正式成为了一名博士候选人。 这恐怕是目前为止我参加过的所有考试中，唯一一个考生只有我自己的考试。从备考到结束，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Question During Judo Testing and Some Thoughts</title>
      <link>/en/a-question-during-judo-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/a-question-during-judo-testing/</guid>
      <description>“When your parents first learned that you were practicing judo, what was their reaction? You know, since judo is a martial art and you may hurt yourself during practice. They might feel worried”. This is one of the questions on the judo belt test yesterday.  Ryan said his parents might have little concerns but they are fine with him doing it.
Taylor said her mom is very supportive, sometimes she even asks Taylor to do some throws on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Diversity</title>
      <link>/vmpm/alpha-diversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vmpm/alpha-diversity/</guid>
      <description>  Alpha Diversity Observed Features  Evenness  Phylogenetic Diversity   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Language Notes</title>
      <link>/en/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/r/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer  To save my time finding codes(since I can&amp;rsquo;t remember all of them), I made some notes here. These codes were all from online resources and I might have made some adjustments or might not. Copyright belongs to the original author, please inform site owner if any infringement.
 C Color  add more colors to a color palette
library(RColorBrewer) # Define the number of colors you want nb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>论拖延</title>
      <link>/cn/post/2021-07-11-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/post/2021-07-11-/</guid>
      <description>我觉得我的拖延症日益严重了，这倒不是因为年龄的变化，而是因为我所需要完成的事情变难了。 就像小学的时候，我最讨厌的暑假作业就是作文，我会早早地</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Kimki (Jinji Pang), a fourth-year Ph.D. student in Iowa State University, College of Veterinary Medicine. I was born in Tonghua, a small city which is located in Jilin Province, northeast China. I got my bachelor’s degree in Veterinary Medicine from China Agricultural University in 2018. I had a good time in CAU and also got familiar with Beijing because of my undergrad life. I have many hobbies and I will not name them one by one here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/en/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/vitae/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information  Email: kimkipang@gmail.com;
 Homepage: https://jinjipang.com;
 Twitter @JinjiPang.
  Brief Biography  Name: Jinji Pang
 English name: Kimki
 Hometown: Jilin Province, Tonghua City, China
  Education Background  2018 ~ 202X, Ph.D. student, Department of Veterinary Microbiology and Preventive Medicine; Master student, Department of Statistics, Iowa State University 2013 ~ 2018, Bachelor of Veterinary Medicine, Veterinary Medicine College, China Agricultural University 2015 ~ 2016, exchange student, College of Veterinary Medicine, National Chung Hsing University  Intern  One Health Program, Iowa State University, USA, 06/2017 - 08/2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>简历</title>
      <link>/cn/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/vitae/</guid>
      <description>逄金吉 联系方式 Email：kimkipang@gmail.com； 主页：https://jinjipang.com； 现居住于美国爱荷华州埃姆</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>自我认识</title>
      <link>/cn/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/about/</guid>
      <description>我是一名学生，74%的人生都在以这个身份度过，并且还在进行中。我想这个百分比还会缓慢的增长，直到无限接近于1，如果我能活得那么长久的话。我生</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>菜谱</title>
      <link>/cn/recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/recipe/</guid>
      <description>J 酱牛肉 牛腱，洋葱，姜，酱油，甜面酱，腐乳，香叶，花椒，大料，桂皮，草果，干辣椒。 牛腱子泡出血水，倒入适量酱油置于冰箱冷藏过夜。取出后加水煮</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>